

# LÊ NHÃ HÂN — DATA ANALYST

#### About me

As a Data Analyst with one year of experience, I am actively seeking a full-time opportunity to apply and enhance my analytical skills. My career goal is to continually improve data analysis capabilities, actively contribute to meaningful projects, and expand my exposure in this field. I am highly enthusiastic about the prospect of advancing further in my career and aspire to become an expert in the field of Data Analytics.

## CONTACT

- **\** 0857025525
- ☑ lenhahan27042002@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/nhahan/
- Thu Duc City, Ho Chi Minh City
- https://github.com/NhaHan27
- https://nhahan27.github.io/newport folio.github.io/

### 2KIII2

- Microsoft Office
- Data Analyst with SQL, Python, Power BI
- Knowledge of UI/UX
- Using Axure, Figma
- Using Github
- English

## **EXPERIENCE**

MAY 2023 - NOW



#### MINDX SCHOOL - MENTOR

Provide teaching support to instructors during classes, including

solving exercises for SQL, Python, and Power BI sessions, grading assignments, and conducting knowledge reviews for students.

FEB 2022 -Mar 2023



### hahalolo llc - data analyst

- Utilize Xmind for report analysis and develop a timeline for report creation.
- Extract data from databases, perform data cleaning, and visualize the data using Power BI.
- Analyze reports to uncover insights. Conceptualize product development
- Use tools like Figma and Axure to draw flowcharts and create wireframes for the product



# LÊ NHÃ HÂN — DATA ANALYST

#### About me

As a Data Analyst with one year of experience, I am actively seeking a full-time opportunity to apply and enhance my analytical skills. My career goal is to continually improve data analysis capabilities, actively contribute to meaningful projects, and expand my exposure in this field. I am highly enthusiastic about the prospect of advancing further in my career and aspire to become an expert in the field of Data Analytics.

## INSTRUCTOR

Mr. Tran Son Hai

## **EDUCATION**

OCT 2020 - 2023

NGUYEN TAT THANH UNIVERSITY

Software Engineer

GPA: 3.35/4.00

## HONORS & AWARDS

MAR 2022 -NOW SPONSOR A STUDENT SCHOLARSHIP

Three times recipient of the "Sponsor a Student"

scholarship from Sunflower Mission

2022 - NOW

NGUYEN TAT THANH UNIVERSITY

NIIE scholarship 20%

JUNE - 2022

NGUYEN TAT THANH UNIVERSITY

NIIE sholarship 50%

NIIE STARTUP

Win the startup with 3rd prize for all school in

2021.